Guide to the Friendship House Association records, 1904-1992 MS2142
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Funding Sources, 1940-1981; MS2142 Series 5; 14.5 Linear feet (Box 93, Box 94, Box 91, Box 92, Box 89, Box 90, Box 87, Box 88, Box 107, Box 111, Box 109, Box 108, Box 95, Box 110, Box 102, Box 103, Box 100, Box 101, Box 106, Box 104, Box 105, Box 84, Box 83, Box 86, Box 85, Box 98, Box 99, Box 96,
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Meetings, correspondence, 1965-1967 (Box 92, Folder 22)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Report - program explained, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 23)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: NDP Directors' Meetings, 01/1966-03/1966 (Box 92, Folder 24)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Missing Services Program, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 25)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Guidelines for cooperation, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 26)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Advisory Committee, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 27)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Testimonies, meetings, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 28)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Community Awareness Program, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 29)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Community Action groups, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 30)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: "What's Going On" community organization, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 31)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Education, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 32)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Citizens' Advisory Committee, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 33)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Citizens' Advisory Committee, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 34)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Budget Request FY 1967, 1966 (Box 92, Folder 35)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 93)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: NDP - General correspondence January-04/1966 (Box 93, Folder 1)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Contract - 02/1966 (Box 93, Folder 2)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Correspondence May-10/1966 (Box 93, Folder 3)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Monthly Narrative, 04/1966 (Box 93, Folder 4)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Budget Request for FY `67 - 04/1966 (Box 93, Folder 5)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Monthly Narrative - 06/1966 (Box 93, Folder 6)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Monthly Narrative - 07/1966 (Box 93, Folder 7)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Audit - UPO-NDP Program, 08/1966 (Box 93, Folder 8)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Agreement - 09/1966 (Box 93, Folder 9)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Neighborhood Advisory Committee - 10/1966 (Box 93, Folder 10)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Meetings 11/1966 (Box 93, Folder 11)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Model Cities Program - participation, 1966-1967 (Box 93, Folder 12)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Goals and objectives, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 13)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Budget request 07/1967-6/1968 (Box 93, Folder 14)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Budget request 1967, 1968 (Box 93, Folder 15)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Education, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 16)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Fliers to residents, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 17)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Narrative Report - 05/1967 (Box 93, Folder 18)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Audit - UPO-NDP, 06/1967 (Box 93, Folder 19)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Narrative Report, 06/1967 (Box 93, Folder 20)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Agreement, 06/1967 (Box 93, Folder 21)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Request for continuation of NDP program, FY`68 - in, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 22)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: "What's Going On" from Community Organization section, 1967 (Box 93, Folder 23)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Contract 1967, 1969 (Box 93, Folder 24)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 94)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: UPO-NDP Program Summary, 1968 ca. (Box 94, Folder 1)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: "What's Going On" from Capper Unit Community Organization, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 2)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Budget Review FY 1968, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 3)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Education, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 4)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Arthur Capper Center programs -, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 5)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Work Program - Component 4, contract, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 6)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Youth Program Budget Report, 04/1968 (Box 94, Folder 7)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Summer Activities, 1968 (Box 94, Folder 8)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Narrative Report, 11/1968 (Box 94, Folder 9)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Narrative Report 12/1968 (Box 94, Folder 10)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Audit of NDP, UPO Grant - 06/1968 (Box 94, Folder 11)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: FY`69 Budget Request - FY, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 12)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Program summary, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 13)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Capper Unit memos, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 14)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Draft proposal, 1969 (Box 94, Folder 15)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: FY UPO request for the program 1970, 01/1969 (Box 94, Folder 16)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Work program proposal FY, 1970 - 01/1969 (Box 94, Folder 17)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: 1971 Budget Request, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 18)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: 1971 Budget Request, 1970 (Box 94, Folder 19)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Program Summary, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 20)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Ad Hoc Committee on Relations of UPO-NDP, 1972 (Box 94, Folder 21)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Grant to Foster Grandparents Program -, 1976 (Box 94, Folder 22)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Contractor's Report - 10/1976 (Box 94, Folder 23)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Contractor's Report 11/1976 (Box 94, Folder 24)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Contractor's Report 03/1977 (Box 94, Folder 25)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Contractor's Report 04/1977 (Box 94, Folder 26)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Contractor's Report 02/1979 (Box 94, Folder 27)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Contractor's Report 03/1979 (Box 94, Folder 28)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Audit 09/1979 (Box 94, Folder 29)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Audit 09/1980 (Box 94, Folder 30)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Audit 09/1981 (Box 94, Folder 31)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 95)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 10/1965 (Box 95, Folder 1)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 11/1965 (Box 95, Folder 2)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes, 11/1965-12/1965 (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes, 1965-1967 (Box 95, Folder 4)
    correspondence
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes, 01/1966-02/1966 (Box 95, Folder 5)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 03/1966 (Box 95, Folder 6)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 04/1966 (Box 95, Folder 7)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 05/1966 (Box 95, Folder 8)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 09/1966 (Box 95, Folder 9)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 10/1966 (Box 95, Folder 10)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes, 10/1966 (Box 95, Folder 11)
    bylaws
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 11/1966 (Box 95, Folder 12)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 12/1966 (Box 95, Folder 13)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes, 1967 (Box 95, Folder 14)
    members list
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 01/1967 (Box 95, Folder 15)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 02/1967 (Box 95, Folder 16)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 03/1967 (Box 95, Folder 17)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 04/1967 (Box 95, Folder 18)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 05/1967 (Box 95, Folder 19)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 06/1967 (Box 95, Folder 20)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 09/1967 (Box 95, Folder 21)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 10/1967 (Box 95, Folder 22)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 11/1967 (Box 95, Folder 23)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 12/1967 (Box 95, Folder 24)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes, 1968 (Box 95, Folder 25)
    members roster
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 01/1968 (Box 95, Folder 26)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 02/1968 (Box 95, Folder 27)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 03/1968 (Box 95, Folder 28)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 04/1968 (Box 95, Folder 29)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 05/1968 (Box 95, Folder 30)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 09/1968 (Box 95, Folder 31)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 10/1968 (Box 95, Folder 32)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 11/1968 (Box 95, Folder 33)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 12/1968 (Box 95, Folder 34)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes, 1969 (Box 95, Folder 35)
    list
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 01/1969 (Box 95, Folder 36)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 02/1969 (Box 95, Folder 37)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 03/1969 (Box 95, Folder 38)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 04/1969 (Box 95, Folder 39)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 05/1969 (Box 95, Folder 40)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 03/197., 03/1973 (Box 95, Folder 41)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes, undated (Box 95, Folder 42)
    manual
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Advisory Committee: Minutes 01/1975 (Box 95, Folder 43)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 96)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service:, 01/1965-05/1965 (Box 96, Folder 1)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service:, 06/1965-07/1965 (Box 96, Folder 2)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service: 08/1965 (Box 96, Folder 3)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service:, 08/1965-10/1965 (Box 96, Folder 4)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service: 11/1965 (Box 96, Folder 5)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service:, 11/1965-12/1965 (Box 96, Folder 6)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service:, 01/1966-02/1966 (Box 96, Folder 7)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service:, 03/1966-05/1966 (Box 96, Folder 8)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service: 09/1966 (Box 96, Folder 9)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service:, 07/1967-09/1967 (Box 96, Folder 10)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service:, 10/1967-11/1967 (Box 96, Folder 11)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service: 12/1967 (Box 96, Folder 12)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service:, 1968 (Box 96, Folder 13)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Legal Service:, 1969 (Box 96, Folder 14)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 97)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Action Program, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 1)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Action Program, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 2)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Education, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 3)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Education, 1965 (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Action, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 5)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Action, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 6)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Action, 1966 (Box 97, Folder 7)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Action, 1970 (Box 97, Folder 8)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Action, 1971 (Box 97, Folder 9)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Action 09/1973 (Box 97, Folder 10)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Action 07/1975 (Box 97, Folder 11)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Action Co-op Store - report 09/1978 (Box 97, Folder 12)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program: Consumer Affairs - monthly report 11/1978 (Box 97, Folder 13)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 98)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Development Youth Program: Request for reimbursement, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 1)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Development Youth Program: Symptoms, reports, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 2)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Development Youth Program: Monthly Report, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 3)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Development Youth Program: Progress report, 1966 (Box 98, Folder 4)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Development Youth Program: Budget proposal, 1966-1967 (Box 98, Folder 5)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Development Youth Program: Audit report, 07/1966-03/1967 (Box 98, Folder 6)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Development Youth Program: Meetings, staff, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 7)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Development Youth Program: Reimbursement forms, 1967 (Box 98, Folder 8)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Development Youth Program: Agreement 03/1967 (Box 98, Folder 9)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Development Youth Program: Monthly Reports, 04/1968-06/1968 (Box 98, Folder 10)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Development Youth Program: Reimbursement, budget sheets, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 11)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Neighborhood Development Youth Program: Friendship House Teen Mobilization Center - final report, 1968 (Box 98, Folder 12)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: CO Unit - slides, 1970 ca. (Box 98, Folder 13)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Friendship House CO Unit manual, 1970 ca. (Box 98, Folder 14)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Activities, 1971-1972 (Box 98, Folder 15)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Weekly Reports 01/1971 (Box 98, Folder 16)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Weekly Reports 03/1971 (Box 98, Folder 17)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Weekly Reports 04/1971 (Box 98, Folder 18)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Weekly Reports 05/1971 (Box 98, Folder 19)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Weekly Reports 07/1971 (Box 98, Folder 20)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Weekly Reports 09/1971 (Box 98, Folder 21)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Weekly Reports 12/1971 (Box 98, Folder 22)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Weekly Reports, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 23)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Methadone Study Committee, 1972 (Box 98, Folder 24)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Weekly Reports, 1973 (Box 98, Folder 25)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Capitol East Housing Coalition, 1975 (Box 98, Folder 26)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Monthly Narrative 03/1975 (Box 98, Folder 27)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Schools - list, education, 1975-1976 (Box 98, Folder 28)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Monthly Report 10/1976 (Box 98, Folder 29)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Monthly Reports, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 30)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Arthur Capper Housing - resident Council Election, 1977 (Box 98, Folder 31)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Program goals and objectives, 1978 (Box 98, Folder 32)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Survey on Ellen Wilson Center, 1979 (Box 98, Folder 33)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Goals and Objectives, 1980-1981 (Box 98, Folder 34)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Organization Unit: Narrative Report 12/1982 (Box 98, Folder 35)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 99)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, VISTA:, 1964 (Box 99, Folder 1)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, VISTA:, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 2)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, VISTA: Guidelines, 1965 (Box 99, Folder 3)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, VISTA:, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 4)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, VISTA:, 1967 (Box 99, Folder 5)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, VISTA:, 1968 (Box 99, Folder 6)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, VISTA: A VISTA project, 1974 (Box 99, Folder 7)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, VISTA: VISTA material, no date, undated (Box 99, Folder 8)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Action Program: Bylaws, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 9)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Action Program: Brochure, description 03/1968 (Box 99, Folder 10)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Action Program: Statistical Report of twelve community action programs, 06/1976 (Box 99, Folder 11)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Action Program: Progress Report 09/1968 (Box 99, Folder 12)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Community Action Program: Quarterly Report 10/1968 (Box 99, Folder 13)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Headstart: Headstart materials, 1966 (Box 99, Folder 14)
  - UPO Neighborhood Development Program, Headstart: Headstart materials, 1969 (Box 99, Folder 15)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 100)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: General files, 1957 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    Folder 1-6 do not exist
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Budget figures, 1957 (Box 100, Folder 8)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Job classifications, salaries, 1957 (Box 100, Folder 9)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Budget Request for, 1957 (Box 100, Folder 10)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: General, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 11)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Application for funds for, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 12)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Budget request, 1958 (Box 100, Folder 13)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: General, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 14)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Classification Plan, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 15)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Neighborhood Service Project - proposal, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    Folder 17 does not exist
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Budget for 1960, 1959 (Box 100, Folder 18)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Income and expenditures, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 19)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Membership report, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 20)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Youth survey, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 21)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Neighborhood Services Project Report, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 22)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Classification Plan, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 23)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Proposed changes to bylaws, 1960 (Box 100, Folder 24)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Backup material for requested budget, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 25)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Classification Plan, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 26)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Neighborhood Service Project, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 27)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: "Day Care for Children in the National Capital Area", 1961 (Box 100, Folder 28)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Election of Hans Klagsbrunn as president of HWC, 1961 (Box 100, Folder 29)
  - Funding Sources, undated (Box 101)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Friendship House application, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 1)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Friendship House application, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 2)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Application to Voluntary Services Study Committee, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 3)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Budget Request for, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 4)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Membership Report, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 5)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Neighborhood Services and Community Center Proposal, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 6)
  - DC Government Funding, General and Health and Welfare Council: Neighborhood Service Project, 1962 (Box 101, Folder 7)